<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Anneli_Faction_Ahmislan.leaderTitle>여왕</Anneli_Faction_Ahmislan.leaderTitle>
  <Anneli_Faction_Ahmislan.label>아넬리트리스 아흐미시안 팩션</Anneli_Faction_Ahmislan.label>
  <Anneli_Faction_Ahmislan.description>Ahmislan Kingdom used to be popular medieval themed amusement parks on many planets. Its main attractions were experiencing traditional lives of thousands of years ago. After freezing of their assets, Ahmislan Kingdom did not disappear. Some remaining employees settled in the wild, using survival skills and primitive tools gained in the amusement parks. They farm, build, establish institution and finally, formed a somewhat realistic medieval society. \nTheir rural lifestyle is surprisingly charming to certain people. After some time, the kingdom attracted quite a diverse group of people, like vagrants, apocalypticists, isekai travelers, cosplayers, armored combat enthusiasts, etc. The increasing population made the kingdom more influential, but it also triggered more social unrests. Nevertheless, the looming crisis did not push the kingdom to achieve more technological advances and social reforms. Instead, residents were more keen on fruitless and recreative expeditions. Althought their troops were mostly defeated due to poor organization and training, everyone did have a good time. \nNow the kingdom is at a tipping point of a total collapse. The society is full of bankrupted farmer, rude mercenaries and idling knights, seemingly preparing for bellum omnium contra omnes. However, rulers of the Ahmislan Kingdom were not interested in the development of such situation, as both prosperity and doom are chapters of their stories.
  아흐미슬란 왕국은 많은 행성에서 인기 있는 중세 테마의 놀이공원이었습니다. 그 곳의 주요 명소는 수천 년 전의 전통적인 삶을 경험하는 것이었습니다. 그들의 자산이 동결된 후에도, 아흐미슬란 왕국은 사라지지 않았습니다. 일부 남아 있는 직원들은 생존 기술과 놀이공원에서 얻은 원시적인 도구를 사용하여 야생에 정착했습니다. 그들은 농사를 짓고, 기관을 세우고, 마침내 다소 현실적인 중세 사회를 형성했습니다. \n그들의 시골 생활 방식은 놀랍게도 어떤 사람들에게는 매력적이었습니다. 얼마 후, 왕국은 방랑자, 종말론자, 이세카이 여행자, 코스프레 선수, 장갑 전투 애호가 등 꽤 다양한 사람들을 끌어들였습니다. 증가하는 인구는 왕국을 더 영향력 있게 만들었지만, 그것은 또한 더 많은 사회적 불안을 촉발시켰습니다. 그럼에도 불구하고, 다가오는 위기는 왕국이 더 많은 기술 발전과 사회 개혁을 이루도록 강요하지 않았습니다. 대신, 주민들은 성과가 없는 재창조적인 탐험에 더 열심이었습니다. 비록 그들의 군대는 조직과 훈련 부족으로 대부분 패배했지만, 모든 사람들은 즐거운 시간을 보냈습니다. \n이제 그 왕국은 완전한 붕괴의 전환점에 있습니다. 사회는 파산한 농부들, 무례한 용병들, 그리고 빈둥거리는 기사들로 가득 차 있으며, 겉보기에는 만인에 대한 만인의 투쟁을 준비하고 있는 것처럼 보입니다. 그러나, 아흐미슬란 왕국의 통치자들은 번영과 파멸이 그들 이야기의 장이기 때문에 그러한 상황의 전개에 관심이 없습니다.
  </Anneli_Faction_Ahmislan.description>
  <Anneli_Faction_Ahmislan.pawnSingular>아넬리트리스</Anneli_Faction_Ahmislan.pawnSingular>
  <Anneli_Faction_Ahmislan.pawnsPlural>아넬리트리스들</Anneli_Faction_Ahmislan.pawnsPlural>
</LanguageData>