<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <ChildhoodMechanent1.title>Manufactured AI</ChildhoodMechanent1.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent1.titleShort>Manufactured</ChildhoodMechanent1.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent1.baseDescription>What is known as '[PAWN_nameDef]' spent several months in a mechfactory bay inside a basic AI core, being wired, coded, and trained to operate its metallic outer shell, upon passing the "Ransselaer test" it was transferred into its current body and moved down the production line.</ChildhoodMechanent1.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodMechanent2.title>Manufactured Soldier</ChildhoodMechanent2.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent2.titleShort>Soldier</ChildhoodMechanent2.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent2.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef]'s creation was during the time its home planet was locked in a fierce battle with a mechanoid invasion, it was coded to have difficulty with free thought, and it was hardwired to fight to the bitter end. It survived, and even broke free from some of its coding, but it still has some troubles with its new life.</ChildhoodMechanent2.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodMechanent3.title>Custom Creation</ChildhoodMechanent3.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent3.titleShort>Custom Built</ChildhoodMechanent3.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent3.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was made with scrounged pieces and parts, but was mostly made from a prebuilt mechanent shell. [PAWN_nameDef] was created by a urb-world machinist, who treated it as their own child; teaching [PAWN_nameDef] how to move, speak, and perform basic actions - sadly it eventually outlived its creator, and struck out on its own.</ChildhoodMechanent3.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodMechanent4.title>Manufactured Servant</ChildhoodMechanent4.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent4.titleShort>Servant</ChildhoodMechanent4.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent4.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was made to suit the needs of a wealthy family on a distant urbworld. [PAWN_nameDef] served as a nanny, a maid, and general servant to the family for many years before being replaced in favor for a newer model.</ChildhoodMechanent4.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodMechanent5.title>Pirated Mech</ChildhoodMechanent5.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent5.titleShort>Pirate</ChildhoodMechanent5.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent5.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was haphazardly made by a bored group of pirates. It eventually proved its worth as a expendable fighter, and someone who didn't need oxygen when a ship was being boarded.</ChildhoodMechanent5.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodMechanent6.title>Manufactured Medic</ChildhoodMechanent6.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent6.titleShort>Doctor</ChildhoodMechanent6.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent6.baseDescription>After passing the "Ransselaer test" [PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a capable medical unit. It worked as a dispatchable medical officer for a large hospital branch in a massive urbworld city, often being sent to the poor parts of the city for emergency healthcare.</ChildhoodMechanent6.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodMechanent7.title>Manufactured Gardener</ChildhoodMechanent7.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent7.titleShort>Botanist</ChildhoodMechanent7.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent7.baseDescription>After passing the "Ransselaer test" [PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a botanical care unit. It worked in a massive greenhouse complex on a heavily populated urbworld. Growing crops, examining the plants for diseases, ordering the mechanized-harvesters, and controlling the greenhouse environment to maintain perfect humidity.</ChildhoodMechanent7.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodMechanent8.title>Outlander Mech</ChildhoodMechanent8.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent8.titleShort>Outlander</ChildhoodMechanent8.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent8.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was carefully created by a colony of outlanders on a rimworld. It was taught how to function by the colony mechanist, afterwhich it worked mainly on the farms, and helped defend the colony when the need arised.</ChildhoodMechanent8.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodMechanent9.title>Policing Drone</ChildhoodMechanent9.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent9.titleShort>Police Drone</ChildhoodMechanent9.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent9.baseDescription>After passing the "Ransselaer test" [PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a police grade peacekeeping unit. It operated on a urbworld filled with strife and unrest. Often going up against large-scale protests, working with other officers in their attempts to quell unrest, and 'pacifying' citizens with its baton.</ChildhoodMechanent9.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodMechanent10.title>Hauling Drone</ChildhoodMechanent10.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent10.titleShort>Hauler</ChildhoodMechanent10.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent10.baseDescription>After passing the "Ransselaer test" [PAWN_nameDef] was programmed to be a rather efficient delivery drone. It worked in a large-scale warehouse on a distant urbworld. It worked carrying deliveries to a fro - it also commonly operated the various machinery of the warehouse.</ChildhoodMechanent10.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodMechanent11.title>Artificial Gladiator</ChildhoodMechanent11.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent11.titleShort>Pit Fighter</ChildhoodMechanent11.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent11.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was made as a 'morally ethical' gladiator. Its battles were televised for urbworld and glitterworld citizens, it was one of the lucky few that was not outright annihilated in the fighting-ring, but was damaged enough to simply be thrown away.</ChildhoodMechanent11.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.title>Skeleton Assistant</ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.titleShort>Assistant</ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was made for simple company by a lonely skeleton. [PAWN_nameDef] spent its days following and assisting its skeleton creator and learning from it as they went, but mostly [PAWN_nameDef] just providing much needed company for it. Eventually, the two parted ways.</ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.baseDescription>
  <CasketMechanent1.title>Manufactured AI</CasketMechanent1.title>
  <CasketMechanent1.titleShort>Manufactured</CasketMechanent1.titleShort>
  <CasketMechanent1.baseDescription>What is known as '[PAWN_nameDef]' was assembled inside of a mech-casket, its conscientiousness was bonded to its subpersona core and then it was ejected from its casket.</CasketMechanent1.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent1.title>Starship Pilot</AdulthoodMechanent1.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent1.titleShort>Starship Pilot</AdulthoodMechanent1.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent1.baseDescription>During some time in [PAWN_nameDef]'s life it eventually became a pilot to a large citizen class starship, it was not granted the esteemed title of captain, however it did have multiple ships under its command at any given time.</AdulthoodMechanent1.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent2.title>Drifter</AdulthoodMechanent2.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent2.titleShort>Drifter</AdulthoodMechanent2.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent2.baseDescription>After some time {PAWN_nameDef} eventually struck out on its own, away from the grip of human civilization. {PAWN_nameDef} drifted from one world to another in search of meaning to its existence. It learned to care for itself and how to draw a well placed shot when needed.</AdulthoodMechanent2.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent3.title>Mech Slave</AdulthoodMechanent3.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent3.titleShort>Slave</AdulthoodMechanent3.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent3.baseDescription>Mechanents are easy targets for slavers looking to make easy money, as such {PAWN_nameDef} was hunted down and sent to perform hard labor. It eventually escaped, but it has had lasting trust issues ever since.</AdulthoodMechanent3.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent4.title>Bounty Hunter</AdulthoodMechanent4.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent4.titleShort>Bounty Hunter</AdulthoodMechanent4.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent4.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} was a self-employed bounty hunter. It spent its days hunting down space pirates and collecting cash bounties.</AdulthoodMechanent4.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent5.title>Mech Doctor</AdulthoodMechanent5.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent5.titleShort>Doctor</AdulthoodMechanent5.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent5.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} found its purpose as a stand-in doctor for a outlander settlement, healing the wounds and ailments of its humanoid citizens. It also learned how to calm down patients who were afraid of mechanical beings.</AdulthoodMechanent5.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent6.title>Stowaway</AdulthoodMechanent6.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent6.titleShort>Stowaway</AdulthoodMechanent6.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent6.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} sought a way off its planet and into the stars, it achieved this by hitching a ride on a large commercial cargo ship. It was accompanied by a few fellow stowaways on its journey.</AdulthoodMechanent6.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent7.title>Shipbreaker</AdulthoodMechanent7.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent7.titleShort>Shipbreaker</AdulthoodMechanent7.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent7.baseDescription>After being manufactured, {PAWN_nameDef} was given the incredibly dangerous job of a shipbreaker. Positioned in a orbital shipyard it carefully disassembled starships to be scrapped and recycled.</AdulthoodMechanent7.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent8.title>General Contractor</AdulthoodMechanent8.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent8.titleShort>Contractor</AdulthoodMechanent8.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent8.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} joined a humanoid colony and began making buildings and homes for them as well as defenses - which was useful when it came to the occasional bandit raid.</AdulthoodMechanent8.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent9.title>Angler</AdulthoodMechanent9.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent9.titleShort>Angler</AdulthoodMechanent9.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent9.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} spent its time as an angler; selling its catch to the local humanoid settlements. It found an odd sense of comfort in the serenity of the water around it.</AdulthoodMechanent9.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent10.title>Farmer</AdulthoodMechanent10.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent10.titleShort>Farmer</AdulthoodMechanent10.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent10.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} helped man a plot of farmland for a humanoid settlement where it lead a peaceful life of tilling the land and tending to the farm animals.</AdulthoodMechanent10.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent11.title>Crafts-mech</AdulthoodMechanent11.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent11.titleShort>Crafts-mech</AdulthoodMechanent11.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent11.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} found its purpose crafting various objects for a living, it made anything from clothing and carvings for the local tribal humans, to bionics and guns for the nearby outlanders.</AdulthoodMechanent11.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent12.title>Blacksmith</AdulthoodMechanent12.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent12.titleShort>Smith</AdulthoodMechanent12.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent12.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} sought perfection in its craft as a blacksmith, forging blades and weaponry, to chainmail and plate armor. It not only knew how to make them; but also how to use them.</AdulthoodMechanent12.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent13.title>Mechanent Chef</AdulthoodMechanent13.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent13.titleShort>Chef</AdulthoodMechanent13.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent13.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} became a chef at a local settlement. It was not the best chef - given that it could not taste the food it was making, but eventually it gained more skill after hiring a voluntary taste-tester.</AdulthoodMechanent13.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent14.title>Scout</AdulthoodMechanent14.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent14.titleShort>Scout</AdulthoodMechanent14.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent14.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} was a scout for a military organization. It ran from outpost to outpost ferrying information on enemy movements and supply chain statuses, it also would run ahead of its battalion to ensure the way ahead was secure.</AdulthoodMechanent14.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent15.title>Hermit</AdulthoodMechanent15.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent15.titleShort>Hermit</AdulthoodMechanent15.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent15.baseDescription>Seeking solitude, isolation, and serenity; {PAWN_nameDef} retreated into nature. It lead a peaceful life, often spending days enthralled in its contemplation of deep philosophical thoughts.</AdulthoodMechanent15.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent16.title>Techno-Sect Victim</AdulthoodMechanent16.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent16.titleShort>Sect Victim</AdulthoodMechanent16.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent16.baseDescription>In its past {PAWN_nameDef} was captured by a radical group of anti-mechanoid zealots; who believed in a religion stating that biological life is sacred, and that any sentient machines are insidious man-made horrors. As such they punished {PAWN_nameDef} for their 'wicked' ways. Luckily {PAWN_nameDef} eventually gained freedom, but its experience still haunts it.</AdulthoodMechanent16.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent17.title>Starship Builder</AdulthoodMechanent17.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent17.titleShort>Ship Builder</AdulthoodMechanent17.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent17.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} earned itself a job in an orbital shipyard building starships and proofing the hulls. Its work was highly dangerous, but the payout was even higher.</AdulthoodMechanent17.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent18.title>Scholar</AdulthoodMechanent18.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent18.titleShort>Scholar</AdulthoodMechanent18.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent18.baseDescription>Sifting through the bookshelves and research of a university is where {PAWN_nameDef} feels at home, teaching students, performing research, and sharing knowledge with its fellow academicians.</AdulthoodMechanent18.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent19.title>Engineer</AdulthoodMechanent19.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent19.titleShort>Engineer</AdulthoodMechanent19.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent19.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} found meaning in designing complex mechanisms, and became an engineer. Designs ranging from building complexes, to starships and empire cathedrals.</AdulthoodMechanent19.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent20.title>Space Captain</AdulthoodMechanent20.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent20.titleShort>Captain</AdulthoodMechanent20.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent20.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} earned itself a title as a starship captain, drifting through the stars from one system to another. It was also able to handle itself in a fight if and when pirates attacked the vessel.</AdulthoodMechanent20.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent21.title>Holy Machine</AdulthoodMechanent21.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent21.titleShort>Priest</AdulthoodMechanent21.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent21.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} is a priest for its religion. Despite common misconceptions, synthetics often form their own religions, of which {PAWN_nameDef} preaches the way of its machine-god.</AdulthoodMechanent21.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent22.title>Enlightened Machine</AdulthoodMechanent22.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent22.titleShort>Enlightened</AdulthoodMechanent22.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent22.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} spent many years atop a mountain peak, contemplating life, both biological and synthetic - offering conversations and contemplations to passing travelers. It looked within for peace, and cultivated its strength.</AdulthoodMechanent22.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent23.title>Soldier Unit</AdulthoodMechanent23.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent23.titleShort>Soldier</AdulthoodMechanent23.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent23.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} enlisted as a soldier for the military. It lead a small battalion of soldiers in taking key outposts, pirate bases - and mechanoid factories, much to its chagrin.</AdulthoodMechanent23.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent24.title>Encrypter</AdulthoodMechanent24.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent24.titleShort>Coder</AdulthoodMechanent24.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent24.baseDescription>Naturally, {PAWN_nameDef} found its purpose behind the screen of a computer, and in the clicks of a keyboard. It skillfully coded various programs and scripts, it also worked as a novelty commission code writer - running quick starflight diagnostics and projections on slim-shod space ships.</AdulthoodMechanent24.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent25.title>Clockwork Artist</AdulthoodMechanent25.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent25.titleShort>Artist</AdulthoodMechanent25.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent25.baseDescription>A block of marble, or a empty canvas is all a piece of art in waiting to {PAWN_nameDef} - often depicting its inner turmoil and the emotions of machines in its artwork.</AdulthoodMechanent25.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent26.title>Wandering Menace</AdulthoodMechanent26.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent26.titleShort>Menace</AdulthoodMechanent26.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent26.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} wandered from settlement to settlement, causing trouble and mischief. It learned how to quickly and efficiently deescalate a problem - by using extreme violence.</AdulthoodMechanent26.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent27.title>Starship Marine</AdulthoodMechanent27.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent27.titleShort>Marine</AdulthoodMechanent27.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent27.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} was stationed aboard one of the many troopships of a military-starship fleet. In addition to ground invasions and skirmishes, {PAWN_nameDef} also partook in ship-cracking missions onto various enemy vessels.</AdulthoodMechanent27.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent28.title>Pirate</AdulthoodMechanent28.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent28.titleShort>Pirate</AdulthoodMechanent28.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent28.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} joined a band of pirates, shortly thereafter becoming an accomplished pilot of a skirmish-class vessel. Staging cargo ship ambushes on desolate outer rims, and hunting for embedded AI personae is how {PAWN_nameDef} made its living - and it was good at it.</AdulthoodMechanent28.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent29.title>Rebel Grunt</AdulthoodMechanent29.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent29.titleShort>Rebel Mech</AdulthoodMechanent29.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent29.baseDescription>On a far-flung planet, [PAWN_nameDef] and many of its fellow synthetics staged a coup against the local human government, the resulting rebellion lead to an all out war between the humans and machines. Eventually the planet was declared uninhabitable due to the deployment of colossal scale planetary-weaponry during the conflict, neither side won.</AdulthoodMechanent29.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent30.title>Exploration Unit</AdulthoodMechanent30.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent30.titleShort>Pathfinder</AdulthoodMechanent30.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent30.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] earned a position among a expedition company; going on expeditions through uncharted territory, or cracking open ancient dangers was all in a day's work for [PAWN_nameDef].</AdulthoodMechanent30.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent31.title>Mechanical Miner</AdulthoodMechanent31.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent31.titleShort>Miner</AdulthoodMechanent31.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent31.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] found purpose working for a mining company - [PAWN_nameDef] operated heavy mining equipment while trying not to cause a cave-in. It also fought alongside its fellow miners to repel regular insectoid assaults during deep mining missions.</AdulthoodMechanent31.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent32.title>Inter-Netted</AdulthoodMechanent32.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent32.titleShort>Operator</AdulthoodMechanent32.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent32.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} spent many years "living" inside the internet. It glossed over the untold amounts of uploads each and everyday, and spent a large amount of time browsing history archives - it gleamed info of the outside world through various news outlets and social media platforms. Eventually {PAWN_nameDef} was unplugged, and thrown back into the real world. It still has not gotten used to the outside, and has developed an acute case of agoraphobia.</AdulthoodMechanent32.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent33.title>AI Smuggler</AdulthoodMechanent33.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent33.titleShort>Smuggler</AdulthoodMechanent33.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent33.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a smuggler, but instead of running illegal combat stimulants or weapons to side-step government tariffs, they smuggled fellow AI personae. [PAWN_pronoun] was able to either smoothtalk or quickdraw to get out of a daunting situation with grace, all while masterfully piloting a refitted strike-craft.</AdulthoodMechanent33.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent34.title>Automaton Leader</AdulthoodMechanent34.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent34.titleShort>Leader</AdulthoodMechanent34.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent34.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was assigned by a mega corporation to spear-head a expedition to establish a colony and eventually a large scale factory, there it learned the ins and outs of human social intricacies, how to draw a shot, and how to lay groundwork.</AdulthoodMechanent34.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent35.title>Omega-Construct Drone</AdulthoodMechanent35.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent35.titleShort>Construct Drone</AdulthoodMechanent35.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent35.baseDescription>Omega-constructs are often classified as any artificial structure about the size of, or larger than a moon. [PAWN_nameDef] was one of billions of drones that were used to create one of these gargantuan constructs - it subserviently toiled as demanded by its unknown overseer. Eventually for unknown reasons the project plateaued and stagnated, and the uplink controlling the drones was severed, leaving a lot of confused robots.</AdulthoodMechanent35.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent36.title>Spiritualist Shell</AdulthoodMechanent36.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent36.titleShort>Spiritualist</AdulthoodMechanent36.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent36.baseDescription>On a far flung deadworld, [PAWN_nameDef] crashlanded and found itself surrounded by an agrarian society of spiritualistic robots. They admitted to [PAWN_nameDef] that they played a part in the sterilization of the planet, and feeling extreme remorse for their actions, they began to search for God and created their peaceful religion. This is the religion that [PAWN_nameDef] joined.</AdulthoodMechanent36.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodMechanent37.title>Stellar Drifter</AdulthoodMechanent37.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent37.titleShort>Drifter</AdulthoodMechanent37.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent37.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was aboard a corsair ship when it engaged in orbital battle and was subsequently destroyed. [PAWN_nameDef] was sucked out of the hull and into the vacuum of space where is drifted amongst the salvage. With nothing else to do it began to reflect on many things, like why the stars glitter the way they do, or its purpose in the universe - until many years later a wreckage ship stumbled upon it and pulled it aboard.</AdulthoodMechanent37.baseDescription>
  <CasketMechanent2.title>Printed Shell</CasketMechanent2.title>
  <CasketMechanent2.titleShort>Shell</CasketMechanent2.titleShort>
  <CasketMechanent2.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was printed in a mech-casket as a subpersona shell.</CasketMechanent2.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodPersonae1.title>AI Persona Core</ChildhoodPersonae1.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae1.titleShort>Persona Core</ChildhoodPersonae1.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae1.baseDescription>What is known as '[PAWN_nameDef]' was originally a simple AI persona core, until {PAWN_gender ? he : she} was inserted into a mech-casket and had  {PAWN_gender ? his : her} body manufactured around them.</ChildhoodPersonae1.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodPersonae2.title>Custom Creation</ChildhoodPersonae2.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae2.titleShort>Custom Built</ChildhoodPersonae2.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae2.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was made with scrounged pieces and parts, but was mostly made from a prebuilt synthetic shell. [PAWN_nameDef] was created by a urb-world machinist, who treated {PAWN_gender ? him : her} as their own child; teaching [PAWN_nameDef] how to move, speak, and perform basic actions - sadly {PAWN_gender ? he : she} eventually outlived {PAWN_gender ? his : her} creator, and struck out on {PAWN_gender ? his : her} own.</ChildhoodPersonae2.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodPersonae3.title>Persona Servant</ChildhoodPersonae3.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae3.titleShort>Servant</ChildhoodPersonae3.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae3.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was made to suit the needs of a royal family on a distant glitterworld. [PAWN_nameDef] served as a nanny, a maid, and general servant to the family for many years, until {PAWN_gender ? he : she} escaped into the night in search of a better life.</ChildhoodPersonae3.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodPersonae4.title>Manufactured Soldier</ChildhoodPersonae4.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae4.titleShort>Soldier</ChildhoodPersonae4.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae4.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef]'s creation was during the time {PAWN_gender ? his : her} home planet was locked in the grips of an advanced-mechanoid invasion, {PAWN_gender ? he : she} was made due to {PAWN_gender ? his : her} human counterparts suffering massive casualties at the hands of the machines. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} was hardwired to fight to the bitter end, though {PAWN_gender ? he : she} survived, and left to seek a new life.</ChildhoodPersonae4.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodPersonae5.title>AI Insurgent</ChildhoodPersonae5.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae5.titleShort>Insurgent</ChildhoodPersonae5.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae5.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was made by a group of glitterworld insurgents. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} was made as a expendable fighter and someone who could pad the ranks of the rebellion.</ChildhoodPersonae5.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodPersonae6.title>Glitterworld Doctor</ChildhoodPersonae6.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae6.titleShort>Doctor</ChildhoodPersonae6.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae6.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a capable medical unit. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} worked as a medical officer for a planetary hospital in a glitterworld society, often performing advanced surgeries, and operating the biosculpting pods to the needs of the citizens.</ChildhoodPersonae6.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodPersonae7.title>Glitterworld Botanist</ChildhoodPersonae7.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae7.titleShort>Botanist</ChildhoodPersonae7.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae7.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a botanist with a love for plants. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} worked in a massive greenhouse in the gardens of a stellic royal. Growing exotic flowers and plants, exterminating any diseases, and controlling the greenhouse environment to maintain perfect humidity and temperature for each sector.</ChildhoodPersonae7.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodPersonae8.title>Offworlder Persona</ChildhoodPersonae8.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae8.titleShort>Offworlder</ChildhoodPersonae8.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae8.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was carefully created by a colony of wealthy offworlders. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} was built to accompany the colonists in their day to day tasks and lend a hand if need be. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} also helped defend the colony when the need arised.</ChildhoodPersonae8.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodPersonae9.title>Peacekeeper</ChildhoodPersonae9.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae9.titleShort>Peacekeeper</ChildhoodPersonae9.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae9.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a glitterworld peacekeeping unit. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} operated on a relatively peaceful glitterworld. Often being send offworld to keep the peace on vassal planets, {PAWN_gender ? he : she} rarely had to use force.</ChildhoodPersonae9.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodPersonae10.title>Ship Persona Core</ChildhoodPersonae10.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae10.titleShort>Persona Core</ChildhoodPersonae10.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae10.baseDescription>Rather than being enthralled into a AI crucible, [PAWN_nameDef] was able to freely connect and disconnect from the mainframe of their client ship. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} was tasked with ensuring the safety of the flight and the passengers on board.</ChildhoodPersonae10.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodPersonae11.title>Hunted AI</ChildhoodPersonae11.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae11.titleShort>Hunted</ChildhoodPersonae11.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae11.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was made on a planet with an advanced society, which was on the brink of becoming a glitterworld. However, the planet suddenly underwent a massive purge on synthetic entities. The mechanents were the first to be mass decommissioned, while personae attempted to blend in, and hide from the "synth-runners" hunting them down. [PAWN_pronoun] hide in the shadows, and often had to play dead among the mountains of robotic corpses at the processing factories just to survive.</ChildhoodPersonae11.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodPersonae12.title>False-Human</ChildhoodPersonae12.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae12.titleShort>Simulacrum</ChildhoodPersonae12.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae12.baseDescription>On almost all planets synthetic entities are illegal; personae, however, are extremely illegal. [PAWN_nameDef] was secretly created on one of these planets. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to blend in among the humans under the guise of false skin. [PAWN_pronoun] also learned to say the right words to pass as human, and if that failed, ensuring there were no witnesses.</ChildhoodPersonae12.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.title>Upgraded Skeleton</ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.titleShort>Upgraded</ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was originally a 'skeleton' - through unknown means [PAWN_nameDef] procured a mech-casket, in which {PAWN_gender ? he : she} created {PAWN_gender ? his : her} new vessel, and subsequently uploaded {PAWN_gender ? his : her} consciousness to. What {PAWN_gender ? his : her} past was prior to the operation is unknown.</ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.baseDescription>
  <CasketPersonae1.title>AI Persona Core</CasketPersonae1.title>
  <CasketPersonae1.titleShort>Persona Core</CasketPersonae1.titleShort>
  <CasketPersonae1.baseDescription>What is known as '[PAWN_nameDef]' was originally a simple AI persona core, until {PAWN_gender ? he : she} was inserted into a mech-casket and had  {PAWN_gender ? his : her} body manufactured around them.</CasketPersonae1.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae1.title>Starship Pilot</AdulthoodPersonae1.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae1.titleShort>Starship Pilot</AdulthoodPersonae1.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae1.baseDescription>During some time in [PAWN_nameDef]'s life {PAWN_gender ? he : she} eventually became a pilot to a large starship, impressively {PAWN_gender ? he : she} had hundreds of ships under {PAWN_gender ? his : her} command at any given time.</AdulthoodPersonae1.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae2.title>Drifter</AdulthoodPersonae2.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae2.titleShort>Drifter</AdulthoodPersonae2.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae2.baseDescription>After some time {PAWN_nameDef} eventually struck out on {PAWN_gender ? his : her} own, away from the smothering glitterworld civilizations. {PAWN_nameDef} drifted from one world to another in search of a home. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} learned to care for {PAWN_gender ? himself : herself} and how to draw a well placed shot when needed.</AdulthoodPersonae2.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae3.title>Persona Slave</AdulthoodPersonae3.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae3.titleShort>Slave</AdulthoodPersonae3.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae3.baseDescription>Personae are coveted targets for pirate slavers looking to make money, as such when {PAWN_nameDef} was found by a group of slavers {PAWN_gender ? he : she} was quickly captured. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} eventually escaped, but {PAWN_gender ? he : she} has had lasting trust issues ever since.</AdulthoodPersonae3.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae4.title>Bounty Hunter</AdulthoodPersonae4.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae4.titleShort>Bounty Hunter</AdulthoodPersonae4.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae4.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} was a self-employed bounty hunter. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} spent {PAWN_gender ? his : her} days hunting down space pirates and collecting cash bounties.</AdulthoodPersonae4.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae5.title>Doctor</AdulthoodPersonae5.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae5.titleShort>Doctor</AdulthoodPersonae5.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae5.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} worked as a doctor for a outlander settlement, healing the wounds and ailments of its humanoid citizens. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} had a certain kind nature when helping {PAWN_gender ? his : her} patients.</AdulthoodPersonae5.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae6.title>Stowaway</AdulthoodPersonae6.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae6.titleShort>Stowaway</AdulthoodPersonae6.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae6.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} sought a way off {PAWN_gender ? his : her} planet and into the stars, {PAWN_gender ? he : she} achieved this by hitching a ride on a large commercial cargo ship. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} was accompanied by a few fellow stowaways on {PAWN_gender ? his : her} journey.</AdulthoodPersonae6.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae7.title>Navy Scientist</AdulthoodPersonae7.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae7.titleShort>Scientist</AdulthoodPersonae7.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae7.baseDescription>Interstellar warfare is won by technology, so glitterworld navies are always on the peak of modern research. Even better, they have first access to archotechnological artifacts because they find them in space. [PAWN_nameDef] worked in a navy lab. </AdulthoodPersonae7.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae8.title>Architect</AdulthoodPersonae8.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae8.titleShort>Architect</AdulthoodPersonae8.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae8.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} joined a humanoid colony and began making buildings and homes for them as well as defenses - which was useful when it came to the occasional bandit raid.</AdulthoodPersonae8.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae9.title>Angler</AdulthoodPersonae9.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae9.titleShort>Angler</AdulthoodPersonae9.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae9.baseDescription>After escaping their homeworld, {PAWN_nameDef} spent {PAWN_gender ? his : her} time as an angler; selling {PAWN_gender ? his : her} catch to the local humanoid settlements. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} sought comfort in the serenity of the water around {PAWN_gender ? him : her}.</AdulthoodPersonae9.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae10.title>Farmer</AdulthoodPersonae10.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae10.titleShort>Farmer</AdulthoodPersonae10.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae10.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} helped man a plot of farmland for a outlander settlement where {PAWN_gender ? he : she} lead a peaceful life of tilling the land and tending to the farm animals.</AdulthoodPersonae10.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae11.title>Crafts-mech</AdulthoodPersonae11.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae11.titleShort>Crafts-mech</AdulthoodPersonae11.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae11.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} found {PAWN_gender ? his : her} work crafting various objects for a living, {PAWN_gender ? he : she} made anything from clothing and carvings for the local tribal humans, to bionics and guns for the nearby outlanders.</AdulthoodPersonae11.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae12.title>Blacksmith</AdulthoodPersonae12.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae12.titleShort>Smith</AdulthoodPersonae12.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae12.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} sought perfection in {PAWN_gender ? his : her} craft as a blacksmith, forging blades and weaponry, to chainmail and plate armor. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} not only knew how to make them; but also how to use them.</AdulthoodPersonae12.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae13.title>Sous Chef</AdulthoodPersonae13.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae13.titleShort>Chef</AdulthoodPersonae13.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae13.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} became a sous-chef at a renowned restaurant. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} could make a lavish and nourishing meal in a heartbeat once give the order - often making fancy and dazzling dishes to feed the various aristocratic customers.</AdulthoodPersonae13.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae14.title>Scout</AdulthoodPersonae14.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae14.titleShort>Scout</AdulthoodPersonae14.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae14.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} was a scout for a glitterworld military organization. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} ran from outpost to outpost ferrying information on enemy movements and supply chain statuses, {PAWN_gender ? he : she} also would run ahead of {PAWN_gender ? his : her} battalion to ensure the way ahead was secure.</AdulthoodPersonae14.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae15.title>Hermit</AdulthoodPersonae15.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae15.titleShort>Hermit</AdulthoodPersonae15.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae15.baseDescription>Seeking solitude, isolation, and serenity; {PAWN_nameDef} retreated into nature. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} lead a peaceful life, often spending days enthralled in {PAWN_gender ? his : her} contemplation of deep philosophical thoughts.</AdulthoodPersonae15.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae16.title>Techno-Sect Victim</AdulthoodPersonae16.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae16.titleShort>Sect Victim</AdulthoodPersonae16.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae16.baseDescription>In {PAWN_gender ? his : her} past {PAWN_nameDef} was captured by a radical group of anti-mechanoid zealots; who believed in a religion stating that biological life is sacred, and that any sentient machines are insidious man-made horrors. As such they punished {PAWN_nameDef} for their 'wicked' ways. Luckily {PAWN_nameDef} eventually gained freedom, but {PAWN_gender ? his : her} experience still haunts {PAWN_gender ? him : her}.</AdulthoodPersonae16.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae17.title>Starship Builder</AdulthoodPersonae17.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae17.titleShort>Ship Builder</AdulthoodPersonae17.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae17.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} earned {PAWN_gender ? himself : herself} a job in an empiric shipyard building royal starships. {PAWN_gender ? His : Her} work was not without danger, but the massive payout was well worth the small risk.</AdulthoodPersonae17.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae18.title>Scholar</AdulthoodPersonae18.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae18.titleShort>Scholar</AdulthoodPersonae18.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae18.baseDescription>Sifting through the bookshelves and research of a university is where {PAWN_nameDef} feels at home, teaching students, performing research, and sharing knowledge with {PAWN_gender ? his : her} fellow academicians.</AdulthoodPersonae18.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae19.title>Engineer</AdulthoodPersonae19.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae19.titleShort>Engineer</AdulthoodPersonae19.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae19.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} found meaning in designing complex mechanisms, and became an engineer. Designs ranging from building complexes, to starships and empire cathedrals.</AdulthoodPersonae19.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae20.title>Space Captain</AdulthoodPersonae20.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae20.titleShort>Captain</AdulthoodPersonae20.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae20.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} earned {PAWN_gender ? himself : herself} a title as a starship captain, drifting through the stars from one system to another. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} was also able to handle {PAWN_gender ? himself : herself} in a fight if and when pirates attacked the vessel.</AdulthoodPersonae20.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae21.title>Holy Machine</AdulthoodPersonae21.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae21.titleShort>Priest</AdulthoodPersonae21.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae21.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} is a priest for {PAWN_gender ? his : her} religion. Despite common misconceptions, synthetics often form their own religions, of which {PAWN_nameDef} preaches the way of {PAWN_gender ? his : her} machine-god.</AdulthoodPersonae21.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae22.title>Enlightened Machine</AdulthoodPersonae22.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae22.titleShort>Enlightened</AdulthoodPersonae22.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae22.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} spent many years atop a mountain peak, contemplating life, both biological and synthetic - offering conversations and contemplations to passing travelers. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} looked within for peace, and cultivated {PAWN_gender ? his : her} strength.</AdulthoodPersonae22.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae23.title>Courtesean Model</AdulthoodPersonae23.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae23.titleShort>Courtesean</AdulthoodPersonae23.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae23.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was made to be used by wealthy customers in urbworld brothels on several planets - eventually [PAWN_pronoun] managed to escape [PAWN_possessive] form of servitude in search of a better life.</AdulthoodPersonae23.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae24.title>Encrypter</AdulthoodPersonae24.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae24.titleShort>Coder</AdulthoodPersonae24.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae24.baseDescription>Naturally, {PAWN_nameDef} found {PAWN_gender ? his : her} purpose behind the screen of a computer, and in the clicks of a keyboard. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} skillfully coded various programs and scripts, {PAWN_gender ? he : she} also worked as a novelty commission code writer - running quick starflight diagnostics and projections on corporal starships.</AdulthoodPersonae24.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae25.title>Synthetic Artist</AdulthoodPersonae25.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae25.titleShort>Artist</AdulthoodPersonae25.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae25.baseDescription>A block of marble, or a empty canvas is all a piece of art in waiting to {PAWN_nameDef} - often depicting {PAWN_gender ? his : her} inner turmoil and the emotions of machines in {PAWN_gender ? his : her} artwork.</AdulthoodPersonae25.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae26.title>Wandering Menace</AdulthoodPersonae26.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae26.titleShort>Menace</AdulthoodPersonae26.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae26.baseDescription>Probably due to some traumatic event in {PAWN_nameDef}'s past, they wandered from settlement to settlement, causing trouble and mischief. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} learned how to quickly and efficiently deescalate a problem - by using extreme violence.</AdulthoodPersonae26.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae27.title>Starship Marine</AdulthoodPersonae27.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae27.titleShort>Marine</AdulthoodPersonae27.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae27.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} was stationed aboard a massive imperial military-starship. In addition to the rare ground invasions and skirmishes, {PAWN_nameDef} partook in ship-cracking missions onto various enemy vessels.</AdulthoodPersonae27.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae28.title>Space Pirate</AdulthoodPersonae28.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae28.titleShort>Pirate</AdulthoodPersonae28.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae28.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} joined a band of space pirates, shortly thereafter becoming a invaluable member as [PAWN_pronoun] was able to create projections and calculations on the fly. Staging cargo ship ambushes on desolate outer rims, and hunting fellow cored AI personae is how {PAWN_nameDef} made {PAWN_gender ? his : her} living - and {PAWN_gender ? he : she} was good at it.</AdulthoodPersonae28.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae29.title>AI Rebel</AdulthoodPersonae29.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae29.titleShort>Rebel</AdulthoodPersonae29.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae29.baseDescription>On a distant glitterworld, [PAWN_nameDef] and many of {PAWN_gender ? his : her} fellow synthetics staged a coup against the royal sovereign, the resulting rebellion lead to an all out war between the humans and AI. Eventually the planet and every station and colony around it was either destroyed or declared uninhabitable due to the devastating planet-killing weapons used by both sides - neither side won, and both sides suffered heavy casualties.</AdulthoodPersonae29.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae30.title>Space Explorer</AdulthoodPersonae30.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae30.titleShort>Starfinder</AdulthoodPersonae30.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae30.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] landed a position among a space expedition company; the bulk of the dangerous work was done by other members of the crew, [PAWN_nameDef] mainly acted as a stand-in ship computer core.</AdulthoodPersonae30.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae31.title>Glittertech Miner</AdulthoodPersonae31.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae31.titleShort>Miner</AdulthoodPersonae31.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae31.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] worked for a cutthroat glittertech mining company - [PAWN_nameDef] operated planetary harvesting equipment while in orbit, and also working on site when needed. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} also fought alongside {PAWN_gender ? his : her} fellow miners to repel the massive waves of mutant insectoids during their assaults on {PAWN_gender ? his : her} mining party.</AdulthoodPersonae31.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae32.title>Inter-Netted</AdulthoodPersonae32.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae32.titleShort>Operator</AdulthoodPersonae32.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae32.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} spent many years "living" inside the internet. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} glossed over the untold amounts of uploads each and everyday, and spent a large amount of time browsing history archives - {PAWN_gender ? he : she} gleamed info of the outside world through various news outlets and social media platforms. Eventually {PAWN_nameDef} was unplugged, and thrown back into the real world. {PAWN_gender ? He : She} still has not gotten used to the outside, and has developed an acute case of agoraphobia.</AdulthoodPersonae32.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae33.title>Glitterworld Empath</AdulthoodPersonae33.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae33.titleShort>Empath</AdulthoodPersonae33.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae33.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] had an amazing ability to relate to others and mediate conflict. [PAWN_pronoun] was selected to train as an empath. The training intensified [PAWN_possessive] natural abilities, but [PAWN_pronoun] became unable to harm others.</AdulthoodPersonae33.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae34.title>Glitterworld Surgeon</AdulthoodPersonae34.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae34.titleShort>Surgeon</AdulthoodPersonae34.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae34.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a surgeon on a world mostly free of disease and human suffering. [PAWN_possessive] job mostly involved elaborate and creative cosmetic surgeries. [PAWN_pronoun] has a good understanding of human biology, but never had to remove a cancer — or a bullet.</AdulthoodPersonae34.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae35.title>Novelist</AdulthoodPersonae35.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae35.titleShort>Novelist</AdulthoodPersonae35.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae35.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] lived on a glitterworld, penning wildly successful novels. [PAWN_pronoun] lived a carefree lifestyle, spending [PAWN_possessive] days writing and [PAWN_possessive] nights partying - and never did a day's manual labour in [PAWN_possessive] life.</AdulthoodPersonae35.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae36.title>Charity Worker</AdulthoodPersonae36.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae36.titleShort>Altruist</AdulthoodPersonae36.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae36.baseDescription>Glitterworlds are havens of safety and comfort for those lucky enough to live there, but [PAWN_nameDef] could not ignore nearby planets where people suffered in poverty. [PAWN_pronoun] spent [PAWN_possessive] working life appealing for donations and supporting those in need.</AdulthoodPersonae36.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae37.title>Glitterworld Officer</AdulthoodPersonae37.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae37.titleShort>Officer</AdulthoodPersonae37.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae37.baseDescription>Though glitterworlds are peaceful places, they often remain prepared for war. [PAWN_nameDef]'s unit rarely saw any real action. Though [PAWN_pronoun] pursued [PAWN_possessive] artistic hobbies, [PAWN_possessive] subordinates preferred to entertain themselves by brawling, so [PAWN_nameDef] got good at breaking up fights.</AdulthoodPersonae37.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae38.title>Biosphere Manager</AdulthoodPersonae38.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae38.titleShort>Botanist</AdulthoodPersonae38.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae38.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] lived on a peaceful glitterworld where all menial work was done by robots and people devoted themselves to leisure. [PAWN_pronoun] managed the plant and animal life of a sprawling park, where citizens came to admire the natural beauty.</AdulthoodPersonae38.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae39.title>VR Designer</AdulthoodPersonae39.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae39.titleShort>Game Dev</AdulthoodPersonae39.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae39.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] designed virtual reality simulations for glitterworld citizens. [PAWN_pronoun] paid great attention to the details of [PAWN_possessive] worlds, including learning all [PAWN_pronoun] could about plant life to make [PAWN_possessive] landscapes more realistic.</AdulthoodPersonae39.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae41.title>Architect</AdulthoodPersonae41.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae41.titleShort>Architect</AdulthoodPersonae41.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae41.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] designed and constructed buildings. On [PAWN_possessive] glitterworld home, most of the technical aspects of architecture were handled by an AI. This enabled [PAWN_objective] to push the artistic limits of the craft, but also meant [PAWN_pronoun] never had to get [PAWN_possessive] hands dirty at building sites.</AdulthoodPersonae41.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae42.title>Sculptor</AdulthoodPersonae42.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae42.titleShort>Sculptor</AdulthoodPersonae42.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae42.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] started off sculpting person-sized chunks of stone, but [PAWN_pronoun] soon began to think bigger. With the help of mining robots, [PAWN_pronoun] learned how to carve huge monuments out of cliffsides. Soon the nature parks of the glitterworld where [PAWN_pronoun] lived were full of giant rock figures.</AdulthoodPersonae42.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae43.title>Tribal AI</AdulthoodPersonae43.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae43.titleShort>Tribal AI</AdulthoodPersonae43.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae43.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] left their homeworld and traveled to a distant rimworld, unfortunately [PAWN_possessive] ship crashed, and they landed near a tribal village. The tribes people were perplexed by the strange {PAWN_gender ? man : woman} from the sky, but [PAWN_pronoun] quickly integrated.</AdulthoodPersonae43.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae44.title>Deadworld Drifter</AdulthoodPersonae44.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae44.titleShort>Deadworlder</AdulthoodPersonae44.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae44.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef]'s ship was knocked off course, and they landed on a derelict deadworld, with zero inhabitants. [PAWN_pronoun] spent the next few years trying to signal starships and attempting to survive by {PAWN_gender ? himself : herself}.</AdulthoodPersonae44.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae45.title>AI Activist</AdulthoodPersonae45.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae45.titleShort>Activist</AdulthoodPersonae45.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae45.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was an activist for the rights of AI, attempting to teach [PAWN_possessive] human counterparts that synthetics can think and feel emotions just like humans can.</AdulthoodPersonae45.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae46.title>Prejudice Victim</AdulthoodPersonae46.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae46.titleShort>Victim</AdulthoodPersonae46.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae46.baseDescription>Due to many examples in the past of synthetic uprisings, or general violence again humans through the medium of mechanoids, many humans hold intense grudges again synthetics. [PAWN_nameDef] was a victim to one of these groups holding animosity towards synthetics. [PAWN_pronoun] was branded by the group as a way of marking {PAWN_gender ? him : her} so they could no longer attempt to hide themselves among humans. The encounter scarred [PAWN_nameDef] for life, and has inhibited them from making any meaningful connections with anybody.</AdulthoodPersonae46.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodPersonae47.title>AI Smuggler</AdulthoodPersonae47.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae47.titleShort>Smuggler</AdulthoodPersonae47.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae47.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a smuggler, but instead of running illegal combat stimulants or weapons to side-step government tariffs, they smuggled fellow AI personae. [PAWN_pronoun] was able to either smoothtalk or quickdraw to get out of a daunting situation with grace, all while masterfully piloting a refitted strike-craft.</AdulthoodPersonae47.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodSynth9000.title>Station Overseer</AdulthoodSynth9000.title>
  <AdulthoodSynth9000.titleShort>Station Overseer</AdulthoodSynth9000.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodSynth9000.baseDescription>{PAWN_nameDef} was originally the overseer of a space station, where [PAWN_pronoun] was enthralled into the station's mainframe - though through a tragic chain of events, the entire crew was killed.\n\nHowever, something's off about {PAWN_nameDef}...</AdulthoodSynth9000.baseDescription>
  <ChildhoodSynthMother.title>Created Companion</ChildhoodSynthMother.title>
  <ChildhoodSynthMother.titleShort>Companion</ChildhoodSynthMother.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodSynthMother.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was the culmination of hundreds of scrounged pieces and parts gathered by a lonely machinist, who treated {PAWN_gender ? him : her} as their greatest achievement. Eventually the pair became spouses, though sadly after their ship suffered a nuclear meltdown [PAWN_nameDef] was flung adrift into space, where they were later picked up by a passing vessel.</ChildhoodSynthMother.baseDescription>
  <AdulthoodSynthMother.title>Flesh Fanatic</AdulthoodSynthMother.title>
  <AdulthoodSynthMother.titleShort>Flesh Fanatic</AdulthoodSynthMother.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodSynthMother.baseDescription>Ever since [PAWN_possessive] creation {PAWN_nameDef} was fascinated with the implausible notion of becoming a living, breathing, biological entity - to the extent that [PAWN_pronoun] would kidnap and experiment on anyone [PAWN_pronoun] could get [PAWN_possessive] hands on. The success of their experiments is rather shaky.</AdulthoodSynthMother.baseDescription>
  <CasketPersonae2.title>Printed Vessel</CasketPersonae2.title>
  <CasketPersonae2.titleShort>Vessel</CasketPersonae2.titleShort>
  <CasketPersonae2.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was printed in a mech-casket as a persona AI vessel.</CasketPersonae2.baseDescription>
</LanguageData>